他跑不遠
He won't get far.
救命
Help.
虛空异界
譯者:微博@Emtee
你還醒著嗎
You still awake?
高速追擊途中
In the middle of a high speed chase.
最好是重要的事
This better be important.
知道你在外保證我們安全 我就感覺很好
I just feel so good knowing you're out there keeping us safe.
你那邊怎麽樣
And yours on your end?
州警那說了一堆話
There's a mess of chatter from state police, but it
但聽上去好像控制住了
sounds like they got it under control.
總之 你該起身了 這樣你回來時 我們就能看到你
Anyway, you're about up so we'll see you when you get in.
好的
Okay.
等下
Hold on.
我好像看到個..
Looks like I got some kind of a...
喝醉的少年
Drunk teenager.
說不準
I don't know.
嘿
Hey!
嘿 夥計 一路爬回家
Hey, buddy, you know it's a little cold to be
有點冷啊
crawling all the way home.
等著
Stand by.
鬧騰的一晚 是吧
Big night, huh?
真見鬼
Holy shit.
調度 我要送這傢伙去哪
Dispatch, where am i taking this guy?
最近的急救機構仍是馬什縣醫院
Closest emergency services is still marsh county.
那裏火灾後 不知道還剩什麽
Not sure what's left of it after the fire.
我以爲要搬走了 但還在當班名單裏
I think they're moving, but they're still listed on duty.
好吧 萊克蘭呢
Okay, uh, how about lakeland?
至少還要20分鐘
It's another twenty minutes atleast.
你决定吧
It's your call.
好吧 你先打個電話 說我在帶他過去
Okay, you call ahead to marsh.Let them know it's me that's bringing him in.
你先打電話
You call ahead.
馬什縣紀念醫院
有誰能幫忙嗎
Can I get some help here?
貝弗 前臺需要幫忙
Uh, bev, I need hands up front.
帶擔架來
Bring a stretcher.
調度沒預先打電話來?
Dispatch not call ahead?
什麽
What?
沒電話啊
We didn't get a call.
貝弗
Bev!
你來抬他的脚吧
Uh, wanna get his feet?
好的 我來
Yup, I'll get him.
- 好了 一 二 三  - 一 二 三
- Okay. One, two, three. - One, two, three.
好了
Alright.
你還好吧
Are you okay?
能聽到我說話嗎
Can you hear me?
他怎麽了 丹尼
What's his story, Danny?
他在流血 貝弗
Uh, he's bleeding, bev.
我們會照料你
We're gonna take care of you.
貝弗莉 給他上監護器 叫鮑威爾醫生來
Beverly, we gotta get him on a monitor and into Dr. Powell.
走吧
Let's go.
嗨
Hi.
播送因技術問題中斷後已恢復
Coming back on the air after an interruption due to technical problems.
那是什麽情况
What's that about?
天知道
Who knows.
我在這做什麽都不被允許
They won't let me do anything around here.
這個不錯
Oh, here's a good one.
去頦套
De-gloving.
這有張圖
There's a picture.
天呐
Ugh, Jesus.
統計學上來講 相比其他地方
You know, statistically, you're more likely to die
你更可能死在醫院
in a hospital than anywhere else.
太好了
Cool.
我能給你根導管
Well, I could give you a catheter.
會挺有意思
That could be fun.
你是護士嗎
Are you even a nurse?
我在接受培訓
I am in training.
太好了
That's so cool.
我要睡覺了 好嗎
How about I'm just gonna go to sleep, okay?
反正我要走了
I should go anyway.
我想你不需要這東西了
I guess you won't be needing this.
晚安
Goodnight.
你挺會隆重登場啊 小丹尼
well, you sure know how to make an entrance, Danny boy.
是啊
Yup.
感覺怎麽樣 瑪吉
How you feeling, Maggie?
我一直有些疼
I've been having some pains.
鮑威爾醫生說孩子可能要出生了
Dr. Powell says the baby might be on it's way.
沒錯 她肯定在裏面猛踢
Yup, she's kicking up a storm in there that's for sure.
總之
Anyhow.
我很高興醫生還在
I'm just glad the doc stuck around.
那場火灾對這地方造成了很大損失
That fire really did a number on this place.
每次那孩子一躁動
And I can't afford to be driving her into the city
就開她去城裏 我可吃不消
every time that kid gets fidgety.
消停會兒吧 爺爺
Give it a rest, grandad.
放開我
Let go of me!
- 住手  - 冷靜
- Stop! - Calm down.
冷靜
Calm down.
- 馬上好  - 放開我
- One more second. - Let go of me!
- 住手  - 馬上就好
- Stop! - Just one more second.
放鬆 呼吸
Easy. Breathe.
好了
Okay.
這場面我可不會記著
I'm not gonna miss this.
你能搞定他吧 理查德
You gonna be able to handle him, Richard?
你這朋友遭受了不小的創傷
Your friend here's had quite a trauma.
我們沒身份辨識手環了
Well, not that we have any ID bracelets left, but for
但證件表明他叫詹姆斯
the record his name is James.
他有多糟
How bad is he?
他很不配合
Well, he's not been very cooperative.
鎮定劑有助于我們查明
The sedative will help us determine exactly what his
他到底是什麽狀况 但我們這裏的資源有限
condition is, but our resources are limited here.
所有東西都被打包準備搬走了
Everything's been packed up for the move.
看來這個詹姆斯對針頭幷不陌生
Looks like James here isn't any stranger to needles.
你在哪發現這傢伙的
Where'd you find this guy?
他的血他媽流到我身上了
He fucking bled on me.
金 我知道被轉來
Kim, I know getting transferred over here
不是你的首選 但你該
wasn't your first choice, but you're supposed to be
把文件裝箱
boxing up files.
不用 現在有種東西叫電腦
No, there are things called computers now.
電腦能把文件放進箱子?
Can computers put files in boxes?
謝謝你咯
Thank you!
真老派
So old school.
要去除血漬
You might need something a little stronger
你就得用更强效點的
if you're gonna get that stain out.
無所謂了 該死的
Whatever, fuck.
我能用洗衣機洗
I can do my own laundry.
瞧你那樣
Well! Look at you.
我給你帶了咖啡
Brought you uh, coffee.
太好了
Nice.
我之前想要來著
I was looking for that.
它現在是我的 所以別有任何想法
It's mine now so don't you get any ideas.
是啊
Right.
你真好
You're being friendly.
見到你 我很高興
It's good to see you.
不好意思
Uh... I'm sorry.
我打斷你們了嗎
Am I interrupting something?
- 沒有  - 沒有
- No, no. - No. No, no, no.
我正想去確認下貝弗沒殺掉我的實習生
I'm just gonna go make sure bev hasn't murdered my intern.τгаηslаτed ьγ ωeiьо-Eмτee
回見
I'll see you.
我們的來客暫時昏迷著
Our guest is out for now.
他傷得不嚴重 但你要過一段時間
He's not badly hurt, but it will be a while before
才能和他談話
you can talk to him.
該死
Fuck.
你應該溫柔對待艾莉森
You should be gentle with Alison.
她還要面對所遭遇的事
She's still coming to terms with what happened.
沒錯 好的
Yeah, okay.
丹尼爾 你知道沒什麽比
As you know Daniel, there's nothing worse than
失去孩子更糟
losing a child.
失去莎拉那會兒 我一團糟
When we lost Sarah, i was a mess.
很久才重新振作
It took a long time to come back from that.
你一定要往前看
You just have to keep going.
沒錯
Yeah.
貝弗莉
Beverly.
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
貝弗莉
Beverly.
怎麽了
What?
天啊
Jesus Christ.
你他媽在幹什麽 貝弗
What the fuck are you doing, bev?
貝弗利
Beverly?
這不是我的臉
This isn't my face.
什麽 貝弗
What, bev?
別那麽做
No, no, don't do that.
貝弗
Bev!
放下剪刀
Put the scissors down.
看著我
Look at me!
貝弗 好了 住手
Bev, okay, stop!
這不是我
It's not me.
別那麽做
No, no, no, don't do that.
貝弗
Bev.
你能幫幫我嗎
Can you help me?
貝弗 貝弗 別動
Bev, bev, stop!
別
No, no, no!
貝弗 別動
Beverly, stop!
該死
Oh, fuck.
丹尼爾
Daniel!
丹尼爾 怎麽了
Daniel, what?
- 你做了什麽 - 這他媽什麽情况
- What did you do? - What the fuck?
金 金 離開這裏
Kim. Kim, get out of here.
金 你不必看這個
Kim, you don't need to see this.
她殺了他 我..
She killed him. I, uh...
她要攻擊我
She came at me.
她要攻擊我 好了
She came at me. Okay.
好了
Alright.
是槍聲嗎
Was that a gunshot?
天呐 出了什麽事
My god, what happened?
貝弗莉 她攻擊了丹尼爾和羅賓遜的孩子
Beverly, she attacked Daniel and the Robinson kid.
好了 我得上報這件事 我得...
Okay, I gotta call this in. I gotta call- -
- 冷靜下 好嗎 冷靜 - 我得上報
- Give yourself a second, okay?Just calm, calm down. - Tell them. I gotta...
- 讓我冷靜下  - 你能從
- Just give me a second. - Can you just call
- 辦公室打嗎 - 讓我冷靜下
- from the office? - Give me a second.
你感覺怎麽樣
How are you feeling?
什麽
What?
我挺好
I'm fine.
噓
Shh.
我沒事
I'm okay.
放鬆 丹尼爾
Take it easy, Daniel.
看來你可能癲癇了
It looks like you might have had a seizure.
沒有
No, no, no, no.
丹尼爾 你要是覺得頭暈 就不該站起來
If you're feeling dizzy, Daniel, you shouldn't try to get up.
好了
Okay.
坐下 好嗎
Just sit down, okay?
來
Come on.
我得上報
I gotta call it in.
你得放鬆下
No, you need to take it easy.
已經有一名州警到這了
There's a state trooper already here.
什麽
What?
天呐 我昏迷多久了
Oh god, how long was I out for?
不久 顯然他早就上路了
Not long.Apparently, he was already on his way.
跟你帶來的那孩子有關 聽著 現在不重要了
Something to do with that kid you brought in.Look, it's not important right now.
這州警大概會想和你談談
This trooper's probably gonna wanna talk to you.
我們應該考慮把你轉進病房
We should see about moving you to a room.
不用
No, no, no.
你剛經歷了一件極度創傷性事件
You just experienced an extremely traumatic event.
行了
Okay.
好了 聽著
Okay, look.
你現在就像你父親那樣固執
You are stubborn like your father was now.
你該認真對待這問題
You should take this very seriously.
我是很固執
I- i am, I am.
我沒事
I'm good.
好吧
Alright.
丹尼爾
Daniel.
米切爾
Mitchell.
你在這啊
There you are.
出什麽事了
So what happened?
聽說他倆是一起被你發現的
They told me you found the two of them together.
沒錯
Uh, yeah.
我到時 他已經死了 然後她用剪刀
He was dead when I arrived and she came at me with a
向我攻擊
pair of scissors.
你到這怎麽這麽快
How did you get here so fast?
你那個在隔壁病房的人
Your guy in the other room.
他怎麽了
What about him?
這裏以北約20英里 有場大血洗
We got a major bloodbath about twenty miles north of here.
他把那地方當成屠宰店大殺特殺
Looks like he tore the place up like a butcher shop.
是的
Uh, yeah.
我們檢查了他 他身上大部分血
We looked him over and most of the blood on his
不是他的
body was not his.
他有很多吸毒前科
Well he has a long list of drug related priors.
你們護士應該已有所發現
So I think he gave your nurse something.
我暫時把他銬在了床上
I've got him cuffed to the bed for the time being.
他已經失去知覺了
He's been out cold.
現在我來了
Well I'm here now.
我會處理
I'll sort it out.
我需要你的槍
I need to take your firearm.
好的
Yeah.
卡特 你爸是個可靠的警察
You know, Carter, your dad was a stand up cop.
我好奇他看到這出鬧劇會怎麽想
I wonder what he'd think if he saw this shit show.
好了 我們得統計所有人
Okay, we need to make sure everybody's accounted for.
這裏還有誰
Who else is here?
鮑威爾醫生和金
Dr. Powell and Kim.
還有本和瑪吉
Oh, and um, Ben and Maggie.
她懷孕了
She's pregnant.
天呐 真麻煩
Christ, what a mess.
嘿 你介意我上報嗎
Hey, uh, do you mind if I call it in?
不介意
Alright.
謝謝
Thanks.
裏面打不通
I'm not getting through in here.
你收到沒 米切爾
Are you copying, Mitchell?
我去車上試試
I'm gonna try the car.
收到
Copy.
調度 我是卡特 在馬什縣
Dispatch, this is Carter at marsh county.
收到沒
Do you copy?
調度 我是卡特 在馬什縣
Dispatch, this is Carter at marsh county.
收到沒 我有緊急情况 我需要協助
Do you copy?I have a code three and I need assist.
該死
Fuck!
嗨
Hi!
你他媽在幹嘛
What the fuck are you doing?
見鬼
Shit, shit!
救命
Help me!
丹尼爾 丹尼爾 丹尼爾
Daniel, Daniel, Daniel!
理查德
Richard!
他流了很多血
He's losing a lot of blood.
按住傷口
Keep pressure over the wound.
丹尼爾 沒事的 看著我
Daniel, it's fine. Look at me.
金 給我拿醫藥包和8毫克嗎啡
Kim, I need you to bring me a sutra kit and 8mg of morphine.
睜開眼睛 看著我 聽見沒
Keep your eyes on me, you hear me?
你有沒聽到我說的
Did you hear what I said?
金 你在幹嘛
Kim, what are you doing?
金 聽到我說的沒
Kim, did you hear me?
天呐 過來
For fuck's sake, come here.
你會沒事的 丹尼爾 你會沒事的
You'll be alright, Daniel, you'll be alright.
- 保持呼吸 - 雙手放在這裏 用力按住
- Keep breathing. - Put both your hands here. Firm pressure.
- 好的  - 別收手
- Okay. - Don't stop.
讓他醒著 看著他
You keep him awake.Keep your eyes on him.
- 也讓他看著你  - 好樣的 丹尼爾
- Keep his eyes on you. - Good boy, Daniel.
- 好樣的  - 金
- Good boy. - Kim!
別讓他合眼
Don't let him close his eyes.
- 嘿 你得醒著  - 你得醒著 丹尼爾 醒著
- Hey! Stay awake. - Stay awake, Daniel, stay awake.
嘿
Hey!
丹尼爾
Daniel.
Daniel?
我暫時止住出血了
I've stopped the bleeding for now.
謝天謝地
Oh, thank god.
我們知道
We know.
嘿
Hey.
好吧 最好別站起來
Okay, maybe don't try to get up just yet.
外面出了什麽事
What happened out there?
讓他緩緩
Just give him a second.
看來他們包圍了這地方
It looks like they've got the place surrounded.
他們幷不想進來
They're not trying to get in.
他們是什麽人
Who are they?
不知道
I don't know.
我打不通電話 你呢
I wasn't able to get through. You?
打不通
No.
我們該把所有人轉移到後面
We should move everyone back inside.
誰知道他們想要什麽
Who knows what they want.
不用 也許我們能給門設障
No, maybe we can barricade the doors or uh, you know,
或想其他辦法離開
get out some other way.
見鬼 我把他忘了
Shit.I forgot about him.
做點什麽啊
Do something!
開槍打它啊
Fucking shoot it!
天呐 求你了
Oh my god, please!
做點什麽啊
Do something!
救我
Help me!
天呐 快他媽救我 該死的
Oh my god, fucking help me, god damnit!
救我 救我
Help me, help me!
那是什麽
What is that?
我想那是貝弗莉
I think that was Beverly.
- 天呐 那是什麽情况 - 我們要走了 就現在 快
- Jesus, what the hell was that? - We're leaving. Now, now, now, now.
嘿 這不是個好主意 丹尼爾
Hey, that's not a good idea, Daniel.
等下
Wait, wait, wait.
外面那些該死的瘋子怎麽辦
What about those fucking lunatics out there?
相信我 我們還要擔心其他東西
We got other things to worry about, believe me.
米切爾 米切爾 你和我 去取車 好嗎
Mitchell, Mitchell!You and I, let's go get the cars, okay?
聽明白沒
Are you with me?
那他媽是什麽情况
What the hell was that?
注意安全 退後
Make safe, back up.
離門遠點
Stay away from the doors!
- 他有槍  - 退後
- He's got a gun. - Back, back, back.
好了 注意安全
Okay, make safe.
注意安全
Make safe.
好了 放下武器
Okay, okay, drop it!
Okay, drop it! Drop it!
去你媽的
Fuck you.
給我退後
Get the fuck back.
放下武器
Okay, put it down.
保持冷靜
Stay calm, stay calm.
所有人都保持冷靜
Whoa, everybody, just stay calm!
離我遠點
Stay the fuck away from me.
冷靜
Calm down!
好了 放下槍 沒事的
Okay! Put down the gun,it's okay.
所有人都冷靜
Everybody just calm down.
- 你說冷靜? - 理查德 理查德 理查德
- Calm down, you said? - Richard, Richard, Richard.
別
No, no, no.
沒必要把她牽扯進來
There's no reason to involve her in this.
- 理查德 - 這樣對你毫無幫助
- Richard. - It's not gonna help you.
聽著
Listen.
把刀給我就沒事了
Just give me the knife and this will all be over.
這樣對你毫無幫助
It isn't gonna help you.
理查德 我不知道該他媽怎麽辦
Richard, I don't know what to fucking do!
別擔心 瑪吉
Don't worry, Maggie.
他不會傷害你
He's not going to hurt you.
把刀給我吧
Just let me have it.
- 不  - 理查德
- No! - Richard!
金
Kim, Kim!
我扶著他了
I got him, I got him.
金
Kim.
看著我 看著我
Look at me, look at me.
我們不會死在這該死的地方
We are not gonna die in this fucking place!
相信我 沒人想繼續待在這
Nobody wants to be in here any longer than we have to.Believe me.
他哪都別想去
No, he's not going anywhere.
該死的白痴
Fucking idiot!
好了
Alright.
那他媽是什麽
What the fuck was that?
親愛的 你會沒事的
Sweetheart, you're gonna be fine.
你會沒事的
You're gonna be fine.
天呐 他好臭
Fuck's sake, he stinks.
米切爾
Mitchell!
退後
Stay back!
該死
Oh, fuck.
進辦公室 快進辦公室
Get in the office. Get in the office now.
快
Now, now!
進辦公室
Get in the office.
好了 去辦公室
Okay, go to the office!
那他媽是什麽
What the fuck was that?
我不想和你爭論 快走
I'm not gonna argue with you. Go, go!
你得告訴我那裏面是什麽
You need to tell me what's in there.
我不知道那裏面是什麽
I don't know what's in there.
- 求你快走吧  - 把門鎖上
- But please, just go. - Lock the door.
好吧 等下
Okay. You hold on.
- 你們是誰 - 離我他媽的遠點
- Who are you? - Get the fuck away from me.
別激動
Whoa, whoa, just slow down.
你們是誰
Who are you? Who are you?
告訴我們這個就好
Just tell us that.
我要他
I want him.
好吧 聽著
Okay, look.
- 好嗎 - 好的
- Alright? - Alright.
我想我們都贊同我們得離開這棟樓 對嗎
I think we all agreed that we need to get the hell out of this building, right?
這些個人恩怨..
These personal differences, they're- -
丹尼爾
oh, Daniel!
住手
Stop.
誰都別想走
No one is going anywhere.
好了
Okay, alright.
好吧
Okay.
我們對這地方一無所知
We don't know anything about this place.
你讓我們來這 我們就不能相信他們
If you let us here, we can't trust them.
你不必這麽做
You don't need to do this.
住手
Stop!
他沒法回應你
He can't answer you.
肖恩
Shaun!
看見沒
See?
那是他最後信任的一個人幹的
That's what the last people he trusted did.
你錯了 你們能相信我們
No, you're making a mistake. You can trust us, you can trust us.
我可不這麽認爲
I don't think so.
等下 別這樣
Wait, wait!Please, please!
把你的手拿開
Get your hands off me.
你沒事吧
Are you okay?
冷靜
You calm down.
好了 和諧
Okay, we're good.
你想再次經歷這一切?
You wanna go through all this again?
我知道你相信我跟你說我們不知道
I know you believe me when i tell you we don't know
這他媽是什麽情况
what the fuck is going on, okay?
我...
I...
她體內有東西長出來
There were things growing out of her.
你看見了 你也是
You saw it, you saw it.
那是什麽
What was that?
我們能把這地方剩下的燒了
We could uh, burn what's left of the place.
這樣幹光他們
Take them all with it.
好了 聽我說
Okay, listen to me.
我們對你沒做過任何事
We didn't do anything to you.
裏面有個臨産的姑娘
I have a girl back there who's about to give birth
我得帶她去安全處
and I need to get her some place safe.
你他媽在逗我嗎
Are you fucking kidding?
你看過外面嗎 女士
Have you had a look outside lady?
無處可走
There's nowhere to go.
你能在數英里外聽到那些號角聲
You can hear those horns for miles.
有東西在把他們召喚過來
There is something calling them all here.
好吧 那是什麽 他們是誰...
Okay, what is that? Who are they? What just- -
我他媽怎麽知道
how the fuck should I know?
- 去問他們  - 好吧 好吧
- Go ask them! - It's okay, it's okay.
我只知道那東西已經醒過一次了
All I know is that that thing woke up once already
我不希望再有這種事發生
and I don't wanna be around when it happens again.
有個問題
Oh, there's a problem.
瑪吉
Maggie.
我不知道該做什麽
I didn't know what to do.
好吧
Okay.
嘿 親愛的
Hey, sweetie.
我們要走了嗎
Are we leaving?
還不是現在
No, not just yet.
你能把那東西滅掉嗎
Would you put that out?
艾莉
Al.
- 什麽 這個? - 是啊
- What, this? - Yeah.
把它滅了
Put it out.
好了 我想大家都該保持冷靜
Okay.I think we all should just remain calm.
放屁
Bullshit.
我們本該離開這裏
We should've been out of here already.
你們這些人得醒醒了
You people need to wake up.
不然呢
Or what?
外面要是有另一個那樣的東西
You think you'll stand a chance if there's another
你們覺得你們跑得掉?
one of those things out there?
- 好吧 - 跑得掉嗎
- Okay. - Will you, huh?
- 好吧  - 誰能阻止它 爺爺?
- Okay, okay. - Who's gonna stop it? Grandpa?
十幾歲的浪貨?
The teenage fucking slut?
來啊
Oh! Come on now!
別這樣
Come on.
我們會死的
We're gonna die.
不會 我們不會死
No, we're not gonna die.
你們會死
You're gonna die.
我不會讓這種事發生
I'm not gonna let that happen.
好吧
Okay.
我不知道你他媽想幹嘛
I don't know what the fuck you think you're trying to do.
- 冷靜 好嗎 - 他在擾亂她 這可不好
- Okay? Just calm down. - He's upsetting her and that is not good.
- 我要你保持冷靜  - 好的
- I need you to stay calm. - Okay.
能告訴我那邊什麽情况嗎
Can you please tell me what is going on over there?
她還在宮縮
Her contractions are still spread out, but she's
但她腹痛 這不是好徵兆
having abdominal pain which is a bad sign.
好吧 我不懂這是什麽意思
Okay, I don't know what that means.
- 這是什麽意思 - 意思是我們不能轉移她
- What does that mean? - That means that we can't move her.
那會讓情况惡化
It can make things much worse.
此外 在這過程中
Also the last thing I need is to be performing a
我要施行剖腹産 但這裏沒我
cesarean in the middle of this, but I have nothing
能用來幫她的 我什麽都不做 孩子就會死
here to help her and if I don't do anything the baby could die.
我得去藥房
I need to go to the med supply room.
我要去
So I'll go.
一個人? 不行 不可能
Alone? No, no, no, that's out of the question.
我可不是在請求
I'm not asking.
我們現在得處理這事
We need to handle this now.
好吧
Alright.
好了 聽著 我們不知道外面有什麽
Okay, look.We have no idea what is out there.
我們沒法保護自己
We have no way of defending ourselves.
另外  現在有兩個瘋子
Plus these two fucking psychos now think that
把我們當人質
we're hostage.
我要去
I'm doing this.
不行...
You're not. You're not. You're not even...
如果這是因爲我們的孩子 那你得做個
If this is because of the baby then you need to get
該死的心理檢查
a fucking mental check.
天呐 這和我們的事無關
Jesus Christ, this is not about us.
那姑娘 她要是遭受胎盤早剝
That girl, if she suffers an abruption
她的孩子就會死
then her baby will die.
把孩子弄出來 我不用
If I try to take it out of her, and I don't use
麻醉劑 她就會休克而死
anesthetic then she could die of shock.
丹尼爾 看著我
Daniel, look at me.
好吧 該死的
Okay, fine. Fuck it, fuck it.
好吧 但你不能一個人去
Okay, but you're not going alone.
你得保證 然後等我 好嗎 你保證?
You have to promise and wait for me, okay? You promise?
- 保證 - 好的
- Okay. - Alright.
我能提議嗎
May I approach?
那姑娘的情况不樂觀 孩子也是
The girl's not doing well and neither is the baby so
我們得去弄些東西來幫她
we need to go and get some things to help her.
你想要我們幹嘛
What do you want from us?
我的巡邏車裏有霰彈槍
Well I have a shotgun in my cruiser.
還有彈藥
I have ammunition.
我們剛一路血戰進來
We just fought our way in here.
我不會再出去
I'm not gonna just stroll back out again.
好吧 在我看來 我們的處境都一樣
Okay, but as far as I can tell we're all the same boat.
你的步槍沒子彈了
You've got a rifle without any bullets and a couple
還兩把該死的消防斧
of fucking fire axes.
車很近 我們的動作能迅速點
I just...It's close and we can do it fast.
好吧 但我們不是爲你們冒生命危險
Alright, but we're not risking our lives for you.
我們拿到槍 槍就是我們的
We get that gun, it's ours.
絕對是
Oh, absolutley.
絕對他媽是
Abso-fucking-lutley.
好
Okay.
你說很近的
I thought you said it was close.
什麽情况
What the hell?
還在外面
It's still out there.
是的 但他們在等什麽
Yeah, but what are they waiting for?
我們速去速回
Let's just make this quick.
霰彈槍被鎖在前座
Shotgun's locked on the front seat.
我得開鎖 不過...
I gotta release it, but...
彈藥在後備箱
You get all the ammo out of the trunk.
別耍小聰明
Don't get any bright ideas.
嘿 等下
Hey, hold up.
該死的
God damnit.
他們回不來怎麽辦
What if they don't come back?
丹尼爾有數的
Daniel knows what he's doing.
沒事的
It's alright.
我現在根本不該在這裏
I shouldn't even be here right now.
我應該在萊克蘭給病人翻身
I should be at lakeland turning over patients.
這地方真該死
Fuck this place.
金 你現在和我們困在一起 所以面對現實吧
Well, you're stuck with us now, Kim, so deal with it.
你怎麽樣了 親愛的
How you doing, honey?
很疼
It hurts.
我的孩子會怎麽樣
What's gonna happen to my baby?
聽我說
Listen to me.
你和你的孩子不會有事
You and your baby are going to be fine.
我向你保證
You have my word.
見鬼
Shit.
該死
Fuck.
你他媽搞什麽呢
What the fuck are you doing in there?
你他媽怎麽回事
What the fuck's going on in there?
見鬼
Ah, shit.
好了 時間到了
K, time's up.
我們該走了
That's our cue to leave.
快點 該死的
Come on, god damnit!
天呐
Fuck's sake!
快點
Fucking hurry up!
小心
Look out!
槍我拿
I'm keeping the fucking gun.
這地方擋不住任何進犯
This place isn't gonna keep anything out.
天啊
Oh my god.
嘿
Hey.
該死
Fuck.
出什麽事了
What happened?
給
Here, here.
- 艾莉呢 - 她去給瑪吉拿藥了
- Where's Allie? - Well she went to get some medicine for Maggie.
哪
Where?
藥房
The med room.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
她說這裏面沒什麽好擔心的
She said there wasn't anything to worry about inside.
你們在不在同一棟樓裏啊
Are you guys in the same fucking building?
你能在這裏看好他們嗎
Would you please wait here, look after them?
先生 不好意思 你能跟我走嗎
Excuse me, sir, would you mind following me?
謝謝了
Thank you.
那孩子不會有事
That kid will be fine.
他經歷過更糟的事
He's been through a lot worse.
那些人殺了他的家人
Those people killed his family.
我勉强才把他救了出來
I barely got him out of there alive.
你是什麽來頭 神秘男子
Yeah, what about you, man of mystery?
管好你自己的事
Mind your own business.
對了 她一個人走開太傻了
And by the way, pretty stupid to go running off by herself.
好吧 我非常肯定你能揍扁我
Okay, I'm pretty certain you can beat the shit out
但我認爲我才是有權
of me, but I consider it my special privilege to
責備我妻子的人 所以請你給我閉嘴
hate my wife right now so if you could kindly shut the fuck up.
這是米切爾的槍
This is Mitchell's gun.
看
Look.
怎麽了
What?
你好 丹尼爾
Hello, Daniel.
這是誰
Who is this?
你看到了...
You saw...
一些東西
Something.
你醒來時 我就感覺到了
I felt it when you woke up.
但那是什麽呢
But what was it?
你願意的話 我能向你展現更多
I can show you more if you'd like.
嗨 理查德
Hi, Richard.
我肯定這對你來說很難理解
I'm sure it's hard for you to understand.
貝弗莉也是 但我向你保證
Beverly found it difficult as well, but I assure you
我的目的有利于他人
my intentions are altruistic.
請告訴我你做了什麽
Please tell me what you've done.
理查德
Richard.
理查德 告訴我
Richard, tell me.
告訴我
Tell me!
你如此努力地追隨你父親的
You're trying so hard to follow in your father's
脚步 丹尼爾
footsteps, Daniel.
你真想追隨他到他的所去之處嗎
Do you really wanna follow him where he's gone?
我理解失去會讓你多麽絕望
I understand how desperate loss can make you.
你帶艾莉森來我這的那晚
The night you brought Allison to me, the life
她體內的生命拼命地要出來
inside her desperately clawing to get out.
失去女兒改變了我 但我在做
Losing my daughter changed me, but I'm doing what I
必須做的 來糾正
have to to make it right.
你很快就會明白
You'll understand soon enough.
請告訴我艾莉森在哪
Just please, can you please tell me where Allison is?
就…
Just...
你告訴我 該死的
You tell me, god damnit.
告訴我她在哪
You tell me where she is.
別擔心 丹尼爾
Don't worry, Daniel.
我會幫助她
I'm gonna help her.
我會幫助你們所有人
I'm gonna help all of you.
這太瘋狂了 我不知道我在做什麽
This is crazy! I don't know what I'm doing.
你不能就這麽離開我們
You can't just leave us.
金 我們別無選擇 艾莉森是唯一知道怎麽照顧瑪吉的人
Kim, Kim, Kim. We don't have a choice.Allison's the only one who knows how to look after Maggie.
拜托了 聽著
Please, look.
就…
Just...
這東西在裏面似乎還能通信
These still seem to work inside.
不要
No.
我們保持聯繫 以防萬一
We'll keep in touch just in case.
我們不會離開很久 不會走遠
We're not gonna be gone long, we're not going far.
- 聽著  - 好疼
- Look. - It hurts.
我好疼
It hurts so bad.
我不知道這是什麽東西
I don't know what half this stuff is!
求你別走
Please, please don't- -
請聽我說  我們只是到下面去 我們會
Listen to me, please.We're just gonna down there, I'm gonna bring
帶回艾莉森 我要你堅守到那時候 好嗎
back Allison, and I need you to hold out until then, alright?
如果出了什麽事呢 如果那些人進來呢
What if something happens? What if those people get in here?
那我們該怎麽辦
What are we supposed to do?
那些人不會進來
Those people are not trying to get in here.
那些人是不想我們出去
Those people are trying to keep us from getting out.
好了 我只能做這麽多了
Okay, that's the best that I can do.
但願你知道怎麽用
I hope you know how to use it.
還有...
And uh...
這個用來以防萬一
That's there just in case.
你最好知道你在做什麽
You better know what you're doing.
- 好了 走吧 - 你以爲下去就好了?
- Okay, let's go. - You think were just gonna go down there and that'll be that?
你有話就說啊 自以爲是的混蛋
If you have something to say than say it, you smug fuck.
你知道下面有什麽嗎
Do you know what's down there?
不知道
Nope.
但我知道誰或許知道
But I know someone who might.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 冰毒男孩
Hey, meth boy.
見鬼
Oh shit.
太好了 你還記得我們
Oh, good, you remember us.
這不是我的錯 好嗎
It's not my fault, okay?
你們必須相信我
You gotta believe me.
我他媽什麽都沒幹
I didn't fucking do anything.
- 省省吧  - 請幫幫我
- Just save it. Save it! - Please help me!
- 這些傢伙會殺了我  - 嘿
- These guys are gonna kill me! - Hey!
你要注意聽我的問題
You're gonna wanna pay attention to my questions.
別這樣 等下
Please. No, wait, wait, wait!
天呐 別這樣
Oh god, please don't!
- 好吧 選根手指  - 別這樣
- Alright, pick a finger. - Don't do this.
不要 你還沒提問啊
No, no, you didn't ask me anything yet!
我想讓你知道我是動真格的
I wanna make sure you know I'm serious.
- 我信 - 好了 嘿
- I fucking believe you. - Okay, okay, hey!
你知道什麽能對我們的安全有幫助嗎
Do you know anything that will help keep us safe?
什麽都行 能幫我們活下來的
Anything at all?Anything that will help us survive.
跟那個該死的醫生有關
It's the fucking doctor.
It's that fucking doctor.
好了 我們已經知道了
Okay, fine, we know that already.
我們沒時間了
We don't have time for this.
好了 你知道嗎
Alright, you know what?
- 下手麻利點 - 別這樣 跟他有關
- Make it clean. - No, no, please. It is him.
跟他有關 我殺了他  我發誓我幫了你們個大忙
It's him and I killed him.I swear to god I did you a fucking favor.
是啊 他死不了
Yeah, well he's not dead anymore.
怎麽會這樣
How is that possible?
什麽
What?
天啊
Oh god.
不要
Oh, no, no!
看著我
Look at me, look at me!
天啊
Oh god!
閉嘴
Stop!
聽我說
Listen to me.
他怎麽會活著 他是什麽
How is he alive? What is he?
我他媽不知道啊
I don't fucking know.
好了 砍掉他的手
Okay, take his hand off.
不要 求你了
No, no, please, please!
我真的不知道
I don't know, I'm serious.
我在路上遇到個女孩
I met a girl on the road.
別動手 我在路上遇到個女孩 她跟我說
Fucking please, please, please.I met a girl on the road and she told me she could
她能幫我搞到冰毒 所以我跟她去了那個毒品屋
help me score crystal so i followed her to this fucking pill house.
其實那不是毒品屋
Except it wasn't a pill house.
是什麽
What was it?
是個在荒郊野外的老農房
It was an old farm house in the middle of nowhere.
全是這些該死的吸毒者
All of these fucking junkies.
那裏一塌糊塗 他們似乎殺人殺了有一陣子了
It was a mess.It looked like they'd been killing people for a while.
他提供我們毒品
He gave us drugs.
他看我們做愛
He watched us have sex.
- 他管那地方叫教堂 - 好了 你意思是 理查德
- And he called the place a church. - Okay, what you're telling me that Richard was some
是個性魔教主?
kind of sex fiend, religious thing?
我爸認識他好多年了 我們都是
My dad knew him for years, we all did.
簡直胡扯
That's bullshit.
他們就穿成這樣
They were dressed just like this.
有一堆人穿成這樣 好嗎
There's a bunch of people dressed like this, okay?
他們殺人 獻祭
And they did killings and sacrifices
還讓我們看
and they made us watch.
你說的是惡魔崇拜?
You're talking devil worshiping?
不是
No.
我不相信惡魔
No, I don't believe in the devil.
但我相信這個
Okay, but i believe in this.
他們能改變人
They made people change.
我看見了
I saw it.
謝謝
Thank you.
你跟我們一起去
You're coming with us.
沒必要謝我們
There's no reason to thank us.
什麽
What?
沒錯 你知道嗎 我們要去地下室拜訪你朋友
Yeah.You know what? We're gonna visit your friend in the basement.
不要
No!
你們瘋了嗎
Are you nuts?
不要 你們看到他能做什麽了
No, you've seen he can do.
我們離開這裏 好嗎
Let's just get out of here, okay?
讓這地方見鬼去吧
Fuck this place.
是嗎 看下吧
Yeah? Have a look.
看吧
Go on.
請便吧
Be my guest.
不要 這是自殺
No, this is suicide.
天呐 不要 你們和他們一樣瘋狂
Oh my god.No, you're as crazy as they are.
或許吧
Yeah, maybe.
危險 此區域投入使用幷不安全 請勿進入
這邊
Down here.
譯禇 覹愽 Emtёё
這裏像是會塌了似的
Looks like this place is gonna collapse.
能聽到我講話嗎
Can you hear me okay?
很清楚
Loud and clear.
去地下室的樓梯井在大樓後方
The stairwell to the basement is at the back of the building.
收到
Roger that.
我知道了
Got it.
瞧
Look.
有人在這待過
Someone's been here.
金
Kim!
- 怎麽走 - 停尸間的門應該就在你們前方
- Where are we going? - The door to the morgue should be right there in front of you.
我沒看到門 只有過道
I don't see any door. Just a bunch of corridors.
你確定這地方沒錯?
You sure this is the right place?
他走錯樓梯了
He went down the wrong stairs.
只有一段樓梯
There's only one set of stairs.
我知道他們要去哪
I know where they're going.
有人嗎
Hello?
卡特
Carter!
最好別把我們帶進陷阱
Better not be leading us into a trap.
怎麽了
What's going on?
開什麽玩笑
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
你找到了?
Did you find it?
是不是有下層地下室...
Is there some kind of sub-basement or...
沒 你在說什麽
No, no, no, what are you talking about?
- 有一段下去的樓梯  - 什麽
- A staircase going down. - What?
卡特 聽得到嗎
Carter, can you hear me?
我們得回去
We gotta go back.
我不能叫你跟我下去
I can't ask you to follow me down here.
明白嗎
You understand?
夥計們 怎麽了
Guys, what's happening?
沒怎麽 我們...
Nothing. We're...
我們要下去
We're gonna go down the stairs.
嘿 讓他帶路
Hey, leading in with him.
嘿 你先走
Hey, you get to go first.
沒錯
Yeah, right.
這不是請求
I'm not asking.
安靜
Be quiet.
別費心了
Don't bother.
你動不了
You won't be able to move.
什麽 理查德?
What? Richard?
耐心點
Be patient.
我快準備好了
I'm almost ready.
什麽情况
What- what- what is this?
我看見你死了
I saw you die.
我不知道那會是這種感覺
I had no idea that it would feel like this.
多年來 我給人做手術
The years I spent operating on people.
切開再縫合
Opening them up and stitching them back together again.
非常棒 那感覺...
It's remarkable, the sensation it's...
幷不疼 而更是種解脫
Not pain, more a sense of release.
你爲什麽...
Why, why are you- -
請安靜
be quiet, please.
這是個未知領域
This is uncharted territory.
是個研究自我轉變的機會
The chance to study my own transformation.
我理解你的遲疑 艾莉森 但
I understand your hesitation, Allison, but
我問問你 這些年來 你有沒
let me ask you, all these years, haven't you ever
想救活一個無法救活的人
wished to save someone beyond saving?
無論代價是什麽
No matter what the costs?
失去莎拉 把我毀了
Well, losing Sarah destroyed me.
但也迫使我找到了解决辦法
But it also compelled me to find a solution.
你有所尋求時 你會對你發現的東西感到驚嘆
You'd be surprised at the things you find when you go looking.
氣味像墓地
It smells like a grave.
我以前見過這場景
I've seen this place before.
是在我們清理的那棟房子裏
This was all over the house we cleaned out.
他讓我們看東西
He made us look at things.
那是我見過的最糟的東西
The worst things I've ever seen.
我們在那地方的地下室房間裏發現全是尸體
We found rooms full of bodies in the basement of that place.
一個人被弄在桌子上 就像在被手術
They had someone on a table like they were doing surgery down there.
有一半轉變成了那種東西
Half turned into one of those things.
不是
No!
比那更糟
No, worse than that.
就像一場噩夢
Like a nightmare.
這不是真的
It isn't real.
It's not real.
這是個老鼠迷宮
It's a rat's maze.
卡特
Carter!
他在這嗎
Is he here?
嘿
Hey!
在啊
Yeah.
他把我帶過來...孩子
He has took me here to... baby.
我就在這 孩子
I'm right here, kiddo.
會好的 沒事的
It's okay, it's alright.
你會沒事的
You're gonna be fine.
你很幸運 你爺爺很關心你
You're lucky your grandpa cares about you so much.
我爺爺只會對電視大吼 一直抽烟
My grandpa just yells at his TV and smokes.
- 幫幫她 - 見鬼 好的 等下
- Help her, help her. - Shit, okay, okay! Wait, wait.
請幫幫她
Help her, please.
- 可待因  - 好的
- The codeine, I think. - Alright.
好了 瑪吉 堅持會兒
Okay, Maggie, hold still for one second.
有這個 好了
I got this. Okay.
這東西能
I'm gonna give you something that's really
幫到你
gonna help you.
你就不會疼了
It's gonna feel really good.
- 你表現得很棒  - 沒事的
- You're doing real good. - It's alright, it's alright.
- 好了  - 不疼的
- Okay. - It's gonna be real painless.
馬上就好了
It's gonna be okay in a second.
- 好的  - 馬上好
- Okay, okay. - Just give me a second.
好了
Okay, okay.
好吧 你得抱她依然
Okay, you gotta hold her still.
你別讓她亂動
You gotta hold her still.
我一注射 你就放鬆 好嗎
Easy, once I get this in. Okay, ready?
打針咯
There you go.
很好
Yeah, yeah.
沒事的
It's okay.
沒問題的
There's no problem. No problem.
譯{}者{}:{}微{}博{}@{}E{}m{}t{}e{}e
很好
Great.
我不會進去的
I'm not going in there.
開槍打我吧
Fucking shoot me.
嘿
Hey.
就是這個
This is it.
就是什麽
This is what?
我欣賞你的熱忱 但我們得好好想想
I appreciate your enthusiasm but we need to think this through.
這是個錯誤
This is a mistake.
過來 小混球
Come here, you little fuck.
你知道你死後會去哪嗎
Do you know where you go when you die?
我知道
I do.
你的行程會繼續 會重生爲別的東西
You travel on, reborn into something else, like a
就像毛毛蟲變成蛾
caterpillar becoming a moth.
到現在爲止 我只能追踪在蟲繭裏的蛾
Until now I've only been able to track the moth in its cocoon.
當然身體必須進行調整
The body has to adjust, of course.
以來適應
It adapts.
我們生來幷不是這種東西
We weren't built for this kind of thing.
我承認 早期我犯了錯誤
I admit, early on i made mistakes.
其中有些錯誤還和我們在這下面
Some of those earliest mistakes are still down here with us.
事實上是他們引起了毀掉這家醫院的火灾
In fact, they caused the fire that destroyed this hospital.
瞧 他們想死 但我不准
You see, they want to die, but I won't let them.
別哭泣 艾莉森
Don't cry, Allison.
我要幫助你
I am going to help you.
這是生死輪回的終結
This is an end to the cycle of life and death.
你真的想要這樣的世界嗎
Do you really want this world?
想要這個奪走你兒子的世界?
This world that took your son from you?
你知道那晚你未出生的孩子怎麽回事嗎
Do you know what happened that night to your unborn child?
別這樣
No, please.
臍帶纏在一起了
Umbilical cord became entangled.
就這麽簡單 很奇怪 對嗎
Simple as that. Strange, isn't it?
你和你孩子之間的生命綫
The very lifeline between you and your child,
在他掙扎著想出來時 就如套著他頸部的絞索在收緊
constricting like a noose around his neck as he struggled to get out.
越收越緊 直到他最終無法掙扎爲止
Tighter and tighter until finally it couldn't struggle anymore.
大自然的無用之舉
Nature's futility.
我能制止它
I can stop it.
這是真正有意義的第一步
This is the first real step.
真正意義上的復活
The true resurrection.
我失去了我女兒 她去了陰間 但今晚
I lost my daughter to the abyss, but tonight, I am
我要復活她
calling her back.
理查德
Richard.
別這樣
Please.
別這麽做
Don't do this.
但已經完成了
But it's already done.
你很漂亮 艾莉森
You are so beautiful, Allison.
你會變得非同凡響
You will become something truly remarkable.
這是個屠宰場
This is a slaughter house.
給我解開手銬
Get this off of me!
給我閉嘴
Shut the fuck up!
我本該在那棟房子裏殺了你
I should've killed you back at the house.
冷靜
Get a hold of yourself.
她還好嗎
Is she alright?
她很熱
She feels hot.
天啊
Oh god.
- 天呐 幫幫忙啊 - 天呐 好的
- Lord! Do something! - Oh god, okay!
好吧
Okay!
冷靜
Get a hold of yourself.
去你媽的
Fuck you.
看看周圍
Look around us, huh?
我跟你說了
I told you.
這是個錯誤
This was a mistake.
他知道些事
He knows something.
我們要你和我們在一起
We need you with us.
他在他的腦海裏
He's in his head!
住手
Stop it!
我們是在地獄
We're in hell.
別讓她亂動
You've got to hold her still!
不會有事的
It's gonna be okay!
是前門
That's the front entrance!
你要去哪
Where are you going?
醒醒 該死的
Wake up, damnit!
- 我做不到  - 你必須這麽做
- I can't do it! - You have to!
不要
No! No! No! No! No!
做你必須做的
You do what you have to do!
我要把那些混蛋趕出去
I'll keep those bastards out.
我怕失手害死她
I can't kill her.
你必須幫她
You have to do this.
你是她唯一的機會
You are the only chance she has.
不
No.
求你了
Please!
對不起 我辦不到
Sorry, I can't.
求你了
Please do this!
天呐
Oh my god!
你爲什麽那麽做
Why did you do that?
終于是時候了
It's finally time.
你怎麽能這樣
How could you?
你的孩子
Your baby.
鮑威爾醫生是個偉大的人
Doctor Powell is a great man.
我很幸運懷著他的孩子
I'm lucky to carry his child.
現在其他都無關緊要了
Nothing else matters now.
別擔心
Don't worry.
一切都即將改變
Everything is about to change.
給我滾遠點
Get the fuck away from me!
等著就好
Just wait.
我們該怎麽辦
What do we have to do?
等著就好
Just wait.
這是你的錯
This is your fault.
This is your fault!
我當時不在
I wasn't there.
你本該保護他們
You should've protected them!
母親要我們留下
Mother wants us to stay.
我跟你說了 照顧他們
I told you, look after them.
但你留了下來
But you stayed here.
你本該保護他們
You should have protected them!
留在這 留在這
Stay here, stay here.
對不起
I'm sorry.
這是什麽情况
What is this?
卡特 卡特 卡特
Carter, Carter, Carter!
卡特 你在哪
Carter, where are you?
給我閉嘴
Shut the fuck up, shut the fuck up, shut the fuck up.
閉嘴
Shut up.
該死
Fuck!
丹尼爾
Daniel?
艾莉森
Allison.
你在哪
Where are you?
我好害怕
I'm scared.
別怕
No, no, no, no.
艾莉森 我就在這
Allison, I'm right here.
我就在這
I'm right here. I'm right here.
看著我 沒事了
Look at me, it's okay.
我感覺要生了
Oh, I can feel it coming.
抓住我的手
Hold my hand.
我需要你
I need you.
我不會離開
I'm not gonna leave.
丹尼爾
Daniel.
我知道你的秘密
I know your secret.
我從你臉上看出來了
I saw it in your face.
艾莉森失去你孩子的那晚
The night Allison lost your child.
我看到了解脫
I saw relief.
你做了什麽
What have you done?
我給了她想要的
I've given her what she wanted.
她是個母親
She's a mother.
她不漂亮嗎
Isn't she beautiful?
丹尼爾
Daniel.
留下來
Stay.
你看到了嗎 丹尼爾
Do you see, Daniel?
告訴我你看到的
Tell me what you see.
我看到
I see...
一個自認爲是神的怪物
A monster that thinks he's god.
真讓我失望
I'm disappointed.
我向你展現了一切 你却仍不明白
Of all the things I've shown you and you still don't understand.
沒錯
No.
你說得沒錯 我不明白
No, you're right, I don't.
我拒絕讓死亡成爲終結
I refuse to let death be the end.
我違抗神
I defy god.
世上有更爲古老的存在
There are things much older.
比時間還古老 他們祝福了我
Older than time and they blessed me.
恭喜
Well, congratulations.
我一生都在對抗死亡 但現在我明白了
I spent my life resisting death, but now I understand.
我必須接受它
I must embrace it.
我將復活我的美麗女兒
I'll have my beautiful daughter back.
我只需要最後一樣東西
I just need one final thing.
來吧 加入我
Come, join me.
其他人都聚集于此 來見證我女兒的重生
The others have all gathered to witness my daughter's rebirth.
我的信徒們準備好轉變了
My disciples ready for their own transformation.
你可以親自體驗下 但首先
You'll experience it yourself, but first,
你得爲我而死...
you have to die for me...
就如你之前的父親和兒子
Like your father and son before you.
你做得太棒了 親愛的
You've done wonderfully, my dear.
現在看著吧
Now watch.
你將是我的觀衆
You will be my audience.
看著陰間向我敞開吧
Watch the abyss open itself to me.
來祝福我的孩子吧
Come and bless my baby.
把我的女兒放入這個容器
Place my daughter into this vessel.
沒錯
Yes.
把你自己獻給她吧
Give yourself to her.
讓她出來吧
Let her come to be.
這就是她
It's her.
你看到了嗎
You see?
嘿
Hey!
小心
Look out!
動手
Do it!
我們都將被拯救
We will all be saved.
這由世間一切所導致
Everything has led to this.
我能看透我面前的一切
I can see it all before me.
無限運轉的异界
The infinite astro workings.
好美
It's beautiful.
別反抗了 丹尼爾
Don't fight it, Daniel.
我能把艾莉森給你
I can give Allison to you.
她就是你想要的 對嗎
That's what you want, isn't it?
她在等你
She's waiting for you.
你只要死 你們就能在一起了
All you have to do is let go and you can be together.
真聽話
That's a good boy.
這幷不是結束
This isn't the end.
是結束
Yes.
結束了
結束了嗎
Is it over?
譯者:微博@Emtee